These files within the Restore folder are deployed to the SQL Managed Instance
They are required by the SQL Agent Job and run overnight to take a backup from BLOB storage, placed there by Tribal
This data represents a full backup of their LIVE CourseDirectory SQL Database
Once restored, and integrated with the wider ASE for the New Course Directory this data is used primarily for Migration from old to new CD
The "Credentials" have to be there first
Then the database is dropped in step ONE
Then a restore in step TWO

Seen screenshot of implementation 


Job to take the daily backup from Tribal, thast they push to BLOB storage. Drop the current database, and restore from timestamped backup into this SQL MI
